

KHANDAKER RUBAIYAT ISLAM

FIELD MARKETING EXECUTIVE

01632091429

rubaiyat2949@gmail.com

Ohaka Bangladesh

Khandaker Rubaiyat Islam

linkedin: Rubaiyat Khandaker

ABOUT ME

A driven & dependable trade marketing & activation professional with the proven ability to achieve revenue target. Passionate in identifying & developing new business opportunity to drive sustainably growth. 3 years working experience of consumer & people management.

SKILLS

7 / 10

CREATIVITY

8/10

TEAM PLAYER

7/10

PRESENTATION SKILL

8/10

COMMUNICATION SKILL

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

AMERICAN INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY-BANGLADESH 2012-2017

HIGHER SCHOOL CERTIFICATE PAF CADET COLLEGE SARGODHA

2010-2012

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

PAF CADET COLLEGE SARGODHA 2009-2010

EXPERIENCE

JAPAN TOBACCO INTERNATIONAL, DHAKA BANGLADESH

FIELD MARKETING EXECUTIVE 16TH SEPTEMBER 2019 – TILL NOW

- Plan field marketing campaigns after conducting preliminary research
- Implement territory business plan through the implementation and execution of trade marketing & consumer centric promotional programs in the territory with optimum use of resources to attain brand volume, segment share, brand distribution, merchandising and other specific cycle objectives.
- Execute trade engagement programs to build and maintain a sustainable long-term business and personal relationship with the key trade members.
- Promote business expansion opportunities to retailers and other merchants

OBHAI SOLUTIONS LIMITED (MGH GROUP)

HELP DESK EXECUTIVE 11TH MARCH 2018 – 31ST AUGUST 2019

- Handling valued customers problems/queries over the phone and provide excellent customer service.
- MonitorFake/Fraud rides offreelancer and fixed riders.
- Monitor Brand Representative monthly performance.

Personal & Other Information

Date of Birth: 31st Dec 1995

Religion: Islam

Father's name: Gp/Capt Rafiq

Bangladesh Air Force

Present profession: Lawyer

Mother's Name: Fatema Zohra

EXTRA-CARRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Participation in arts, painting, clay modeling.
- Android Studio and App development.
- Participation in National TV drama series, college football team, world cyber games.

MICROSOFT OFFICE

5/10 EXCEL 8/10 WORD 6/10 POWER PONT

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

FRONT OFFICE

THE WESTIN DHAKA

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Can use operating system Windows 10.
- Web designing andWordPress.
- Web browsing & email.
- IT: MS Office (Microsoft word, excel, PowerPoint etc.).

REFERENCE

MD AL AMIN HAFIZ

AREA SALES MANAGER
JAPAN TOBACCO INTERNATIONAL

SHAFI MD HOSSAIN

SENIOR EXECUTIVE
MGH GROUP

TUSHAR QAZI YAMIN KABIR

MANAGER, MARKETING OPERATION IDP BANGLADESH

PART TIME & CASUAL EXPERIENCE

- AIUB Film Club 2015 2017
- AIUB Tourism Club 2016 2017
- Portraits, wedding & documentary Photography 2013 2017
- IFAD Zero Co2 Cycle Ride Organized by BDcyclist 2016
- Participation in World Cyber Games 2005 –2007
- Worked in media (YouTube, Online AV, National TV) 2013 2018